<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>UN Online Mills</title>
	<atom:link href="https://un.online.mills.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://un.online.mills.edu/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 02:31:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://un.online.mills.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/un-online.png</url>
	<title>UN Online Mills</title>
	<link>https://un.online.mills.edu/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Building a playbook for elite-level sports</title>
		<link>https://un.online.mills.edu/building-a-playbook-for-elite-level-sports/</link>
					<comments>https://un.online.mills.edu/building-a-playbook-for-elite-level-sports/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 02:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://un.online.mills.edu/?p=28</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Master’s student Jerry Lu works to optimize the performance of both athletes and their sporting organizations. “All I did was swim,” says Jerry Lu, recalling his teenage years as a competitive swimmer. “From age 12 to 19, it was close to 30 hours a week of training.” Although Lu no longer competes himself, his understanding</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://un.online.mills.edu/building-a-playbook-for-elite-level-sports/">Building a playbook for elite-level sports</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://un.online.mills.edu">UN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Master’s student Jerry Lu works to optimize the performance of both athletes and their sporting organizations.</p>



<p>“All I did was swim,” says Jerry Lu, recalling his teenage years as a competitive swimmer. “From age 12 to 19, it was close to 30 hours a week of training.” Although Lu no longer competes himself, his understanding of the dedication and impeccable technique required in elite sports continues to shape his path as a master’s student at the MIT Sloan School of Management.</p>



<p>As an undergraduate at the University of Virginia, Lu majored in systems and information engineering and economics. He had stopped swimming competitively, but he stayed connected to the sport as a technical performance consultant for the university’s nationally ranked swim team. Under his advisor, Ken Ono, Lu built a methodology of analyzing data from sensors worn by swimmers to improve their individual performance. By looking at an athlete’s propulsion and drag data over the course of a race, Lu can advise them on where they can shave off tenths of a second simply by adjusting their stroke to be more efficient.</p>



<p>That experience inspired Lu to pursue a career in other aspects of sports. At MIT he’s pursuing a master’s in finance to build the analytical skills necessary to enable the sustainability of sports that don’t already enjoy the major commercial success of, say, football or basketball. It’s especially a challenge for Olympic sports, such as swimming, which struggle for commercial ventures outside of Olympic years.</p>



<p>“My work in swimming is focused on athlete performance to win, but the definition of winning is different for a sport as a whole, and for an organization,” Lu says. “Not only do you need to win medals, a big part of it is how you allocate money because you also need to grow your sport.”</p>



<p>At MIT, Lu is building a playbook for high-performance sports from both an athletic and financial perspective. He’s been gaining exposure to additional elite sports by working with MIT’s Sports Lab under Professor Anette “Peko” Hosoi. His work there isn’t a requirement for his master’s program, but Lu appreciates that the program’s flexibility allows him time to pursue research that interests him, alongside the required curriculum.</p>



<p>“I’m quite lucky to be here in the sense that MIT is known to train great people in engineering, &nbsp;science, or business, but also people with unique passions,” says Lu. “People that love football drafting, people that love to understand how you throw a curveball — they use their knowledge in very unexpected ways, and that’s when innovation happens.”</p>



<p>Lu’s research with the Sports Lab focuses on optimizing strategies for aesthetic sports, such as figure skating or snowboarding, which are judged very differently than swimming is. Instead of figuring out how to move faster, athletes are interested in structuring routines that net them the most points from a panel of judges. Modelling techniques can be helpful for figuring out how to put together routines to maximize an athlete’s abilities, and also to predict how a judge might assign points based on how or when a skill is demonstrated. Optimizing both athletic performance and judge psychology is a challenge, it’s this type of innovation that excites him. He hopes more sporting organizations will adopt similar data-driven strategies in the future.</p>



<p>When asked where he’d like to end up after finishing his degree, “The sport industry is the natural choice,” Lu says. Though he is certain his career will lead to sports eventually, he is still open to exploring new paths. This summer he will be a trading intern at Citadel Securities to apply the concepts learned in his degree program courses. He’s also picked up sailing since coming to MIT, already reaching the highest amateur rating in under a year. Lu consistently strives for excellence, whether in himself or for those he works with.</p>



<p>Since graduating from UVA, Lu has continued to work with swimmers, including national champions and Olympic medalists, as a technical performance consultant. He’s also branched out into another Olympic sport, triathlon. Lu describes it as a side gig, but he’s deeply invested in the athletes he works with, even taking trips to the Olympic Training Center to collect data and help them build strategies for improvement.</p>



<p>“The most fun part is actually interacting with the athletes and engaging and understanding how they think,” says Lu. “It’s easier for me to do so than others, because if you’ve never swam before and you’ve never trained as an elite athlete before, it’s hard to understand what exactly you can and cannot do and how to communicate these things to a coach or an athlete.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://un.online.mills.edu/building-a-playbook-for-elite-level-sports/">Building a playbook for elite-level sports</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://un.online.mills.edu">UN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://un.online.mills.edu/building-a-playbook-for-elite-level-sports/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Declan Rice Arsenal opening bid for England international midfielder turned down by West Ham</title>
		<link>https://un.online.mills.edu/declan-rice-arsenal-opening-bid-for-england-international-midfielder-turned-down-by-west-ham/</link>
					<comments>https://un.online.mills.edu/declan-rice-arsenal-opening-bid-for-england-international-midfielder-turned-down-by-west-ham/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 02:29:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://un.online.mills.edu/?p=25</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>West Ham have rejected Arsenal&#8217;s opening bid for Declan Rice, thought to be worth £80m plus add-ons. The Gunners&#8217; opening offer would have been paid in slow instalments with a lot of tough contingencies attached to it. West Ham&#8217;s valuation of Rice remains £120m but it is understood the club would accept £100m plus a</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://un.online.mills.edu/declan-rice-arsenal-opening-bid-for-england-international-midfielder-turned-down-by-west-ham/">Declan Rice Arsenal opening bid for England international midfielder turned down by West Ham</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://un.online.mills.edu">UN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>West Ham have rejected Arsenal&#8217;s opening bid for Declan Rice, thought to be worth £80m plus add-ons.</p>



<p>The Gunners&#8217; opening offer would have been paid in slow instalments with a lot of tough contingencies attached to it. West Ham&#8217;s valuation of Rice remains £120m but it is understood the club would accept £100m plus a player.</p>



<p>Arsenal remain in talks with West Ham and the expected second bid &#8211; when it is submitted &#8211; could be worth more than £100m.</p>



<p>They will have to improve the value and structure of their bid significantly if they want to sign the player. Manchester City are also keeping an eye on Rice&#8217;s situation.</p>



<p>David Sullivan, West Ham&#8217;s chairman, revealed in the wake of the club&#8217;s Europa Conference League victory earlier this month that the 24-year-old will be allowed to leave this summer.</p>



<p>Manchester United and Bayern Munich have also held an interest in the England international, who became only the third West Ham captain to lift a major trophy when they beat Fiorentina in Prague.</p>



<p>Rice has two years remaining on his contract but asked whether the Europa Conference League win would be his final act for the club, Sullivan told <em>talkSPORT</em>: &#8220;I think it has to be. We promised him he could go</p>



<p>Remaining Time&nbsp;0:00As speculation mounts over Declan Rice&#8217;s future we take a look at his best Premier League moments for West Ham</p>



<p>&#8220;He set his heart on going and in due course he has to get on and we have to get a replacement.</p>



<p>&#8220;It is not something we wanted to happen. We offered him £200,000 a week 18 months ago and he turned it down. You can&#8217;t keep a player who doesn&#8217;t want to be there.</p>



<p>&#8220;I think the offers will start to come. Three or four clubs have shown interest but out of respect to West Ham, while we&#8217;re still playing, you don&#8217;t make offers for players.&#8221;</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">&#8216;My future is up to the people above&#8217;</h3>



<p>Remaining Time&nbsp;0:00Declan Rice said he was trying to appreciate the moment as West Ham showed off the Europa Conference League trophy in east London</p>



<p>Rice declared his love for West Ham following the victory in Prague but admitted he does not know whether he will still be at the club next season.</p>



<p>&#8220;I&#8217;ve still got two years left,&#8221; Rice told&nbsp;<em>Sky Sports News</em>.</p>



<p>&#8220;There&#8217;s so much speculation &#8211; I see it all the time &#8211; but I can&#8217;t help that. That comes with playing football every day and doing what I do.</p>



<p>Remaining Time&nbsp;0:00West Ham captain Declan Rice says he was lost for words after winning the &#8216;special&#8217; Europa Conference League against Fiorentina in Prague and admits he does not know whether he will still be at the club next season</p>



<p>&#8220;My focus, and it has been since the World Cup, is to win this trophy and keep West Ham in the Premier League.&#8221;</p>



<p>He added: &#8220;I genuinely don&#8217;t know what&#8217;s happening at the minute. That is my honest answer.</p>



<p>&#8220;To read it myself [the speculation], it&#8217;s actually getting quite boring. Who knows what is going to happen? It&#8217;s flattering to be wanted by a lot of clubs but the badge on my chest is West Ham.</p>



<p>&#8220;I&#8217;ve still got two years left on my contract and ultimately it is up to the people above.&#8221;</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Follow the summer transfer window with Sky Sports</strong></h3>



<p>Who will be on the move this summer when the transfer window opens on June 14 and closes at 11pm on September 1 in England and midnight in Scotland?</p>



<p>Keep up to date with all the latest transfer news and rumours in our dedicated Transfer Centre blog on Sky Sports&#8217; digital platforms. You can also catch up with the ins, outs and analysis on Sky Sports News.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://un.online.mills.edu/declan-rice-arsenal-opening-bid-for-england-international-midfielder-turned-down-by-west-ham/">Declan Rice Arsenal opening bid for England international midfielder turned down by West Ham</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://un.online.mills.edu">UN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://un.online.mills.edu/declan-rice-arsenal-opening-bid-for-england-international-midfielder-turned-down-by-west-ham/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Intercontinental Cup: India, Lebanon play out goalless draw</title>
		<link>https://un.online.mills.edu/intercontinental-cup-india-lebanon-play-out-goalless-draw/</link>
					<comments>https://un.online.mills.edu/intercontinental-cup-india-lebanon-play-out-goalless-draw/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 02:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://un.online.mills.edu/?p=21</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Continuing with his policy to make wholesome changes to his starting XI, head coach Igor Stimac benched a number of seniors including striker Sunil Chhetri and goalkeeper Gurpreet Singh Sandhu. India missed the chances that came their way to settle for a goalless draw with Lebanon in the Intercontinental Cup football tournament here on Thursday.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://un.online.mills.edu/intercontinental-cup-india-lebanon-play-out-goalless-draw/">Intercontinental Cup: India, Lebanon play out goalless draw</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://un.online.mills.edu">UN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Continuing with his policy to make wholesome changes to his starting XI, head coach Igor Stimac benched a number of seniors including striker Sunil Chhetri and goalkeeper Gurpreet Singh Sandhu.</p>



<p>India missed the chances that came their way to settle for a goalless draw with Lebanon in the Intercontinental Cup football tournament here on Thursday.</p>



<p>Continuing with his policy to make wholesome changes to his starting XI, head coach Igor Stimac benched a number of seniors including striker Sunil Chhetri and goalkeeper Gurpreet Singh Sandhu.</p>



<p>Defensive linchpin Sandesh Jhingan wore the captain’s armband in Chhetri’s absence.</p>



<p>The result however did not matter as both teams had already sealed their places in the final of the four-nation tournament. Mongolia and Vanuatu were the two other teams taking part in the event.</p>



<p>Introduced in the 82nd minute, Chhetri received a perfect delivery from Anirudh Thapa but the India captain could not find the back of the net.</p>



<p>It would have been 1-0 India within the first five minutes of the game but, after being set up by Lallianzuala Chhangte and with just the opposition goalkeeper to beat, Anirudh Thapa missed a sitter on the fourth minute. All he could do was shoot the ball away.</p>



<p>Then, almost 20 minutes into the match, another chance was wasted as Ashique Kuruniyan hit the ball straight to the Lebanese goalkeeper after a good ball inside the box.</p>



<p>The two missed chances from India meant the teams went into the half-time break goalless.</p>



<p>It pretty much continued in the same way in the second half, which also saw the floodlights going off for a couple of minutes, as both teams failed to failed to find the target.</p>



<p>Hoping to break the deadlock, both India and Lebanon rang in a few changes, but to no avail as the score remained unchanged till the final whistle.</p>



<p>India had kicked off their campaign with a 2-0 win over Mongolia last Friday before beating Vanuatu 1-0 three days later on Monday.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://un.online.mills.edu/intercontinental-cup-india-lebanon-play-out-goalless-draw/">Intercontinental Cup: India, Lebanon play out goalless draw</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://un.online.mills.edu">UN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://un.online.mills.edu/intercontinental-cup-india-lebanon-play-out-goalless-draw/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cristiano Ronaldo reveals the meaning of his iconic ‘Siuuuu’ celebration</title>
		<link>https://un.online.mills.edu/cristiano-ronaldo-reveals-the-meaning-of-his-iconic-siuuuu-celebration/</link>
					<comments>https://un.online.mills.edu/cristiano-ronaldo-reveals-the-meaning-of-his-iconic-siuuuu-celebration/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 02:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://un.online.mills.edu/?p=18</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cristiano Ronaldo reveals the meaning of his iconic ‘Siuuuu’ celebration Cristiano Ronaldo’s “siuu” celebration is one of the most iconic in sports. The Portuguese superstar first performed the celebration in 2013, after scoring a goal for Real Madrid against Chelsea in the UEFA Champions League. Since then, he has done it countless times, and it</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://un.online.mills.edu/cristiano-ronaldo-reveals-the-meaning-of-his-iconic-siuuuu-celebration/">Cristiano Ronaldo reveals the meaning of his iconic ‘Siuuuu’ celebration</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://un.online.mills.edu">UN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Cristiano Ronaldo reveals the meaning of his iconic ‘Siuuuu’ celebration</p>



<p>Cristiano Ronaldo’s “siuu” celebration is one of the most iconic in sports. The Portuguese superstar first performed the celebration in 2013, after scoring a goal for Real Madrid against Chelsea in the UEFA Champions League.</p>



<p>Since then, he has done it countless times, and it has become an important part of his game.</p>



<p>The “Siu” celebration is simple yet effective as Ronaldo runs towards the goal, jumps into the air, and does a mid-air pirouette. As he lands, he shouts “Si!”</p>



<p>Ever since, this celebration has been copied by many other players and individuals across the globe.</p>



<p>Now speaking on it, Ronaldo in a chat with LiveScore, for whom he is an official global brand ambassador, said, “It seems to have grown into its own global phenomenon – and I love when I see other players doing it, or people send me videos of people in other sports doing it or little kids doing it – it’s great. It means yes – very simple but meaning it strongly!”</p>



<p>Ronaldo had also spoken about it earlier where he said: “I started to say ‘si’, it’s like ‘yes’, when I was in Real Madrid. I was in the USA and we played against Chelsea and I don’t know where this is coming from, the celebration,” he said. “I just scored the goal and it just came out. It was just natural, to be honest. Since that, I started to do it more often and I feel like the supporters and the fans see it and they’re like ‘Cristiano, siiiiiiuuuu’. I’m like ‘wow! People are reminded of me because of it!’ So it’s good, and I’ll continue doing it like that.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://un.online.mills.edu/cristiano-ronaldo-reveals-the-meaning-of-his-iconic-siuuuu-celebration/">Cristiano Ronaldo reveals the meaning of his iconic ‘Siuuuu’ celebration</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://un.online.mills.edu">UN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://un.online.mills.edu/cristiano-ronaldo-reveals-the-meaning-of-his-iconic-siuuuu-celebration/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Explore Miami Beach from the bottom to the top. Here are some of its hidden gems</title>
		<link>https://un.online.mills.edu/explore-miami-beach-from-the-bottom-to-the-top-here-are-some-of-its-hidden-gems/</link>
					<comments>https://un.online.mills.edu/explore-miami-beach-from-the-bottom-to-the-top-here-are-some-of-its-hidden-gems/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 01:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://un.online.mills.edu/?p=5</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Explore Miami Beach from the bottom to the top. Here are some of its hidden gems Miami Beach is like an encyclopedia of the best of 20th century architecture. There are 14 historic districts comprising more than 2,600 protected buildings, along with four National Register historic districts. The main architectural styles generally go by decade</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://un.online.mills.edu/explore-miami-beach-from-the-bottom-to-the-top-here-are-some-of-its-hidden-gems/">Explore Miami Beach from the bottom to the top. Here are some of its hidden gems</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://un.online.mills.edu">UN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Explore Miami Beach from the bottom to the top. Here are some of its hidden gems</p>



<p>Miami Beach is like an encyclopedia of the best of 20th century architecture.</p>



<p>There are 14 historic districts comprising more than 2,600 protected buildings, along with four National Register historic districts. The main architectural styles generally go by decade — from the Mediterranean 1920s, Art Deco 1930s and ‘40s, and MiMo 1950s and ‘60s.</p>



<p>&nbsp;This story is a subscriber exclusive</p>



<p>South Beach is a dense, walkable playground with beaches, Art Deco architecture, and the Atlantic Ocean. In Mid Beach, stately homes on the west side of the island coexist with oceanfront resort hotels and condominiums on the east. North Beach — which saw its major development in the 1950s and ‘60s — is now home to two Miami Modern historic districts.</p>



<p>Whether exploring by foot, bicycle or car, there is an abundance of visual, cultural, and artistic delights to enjoy on a stroll around Miami Beach.</p>



<p>Here are my five favorite spots in Miami Beach:</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">South Beach</h3>



<p><strong>South Pointe Park,</strong>&nbsp;1 Washington Ave.</p>



<p>A visit to South Pointe Park at any time of the day is bound to bring a smile to visitors. In the morning, watch as the sun rises over the native garden plantings overlooking South Pointe Park Pier and the iconic Miami Beach lifeguard towers. Free yoga classes are offered regularly nearby — it’s a great way to start off the day surrounded by nature’s beauty.</p>



<p><strong>Tip:&nbsp;</strong>At sunset, watch the sun disappear behind the high rises in downtown Miami, while drum circles and yogis celebrate its departure underneath a pastel-colored sky.</p>



<p><strong>Art Deco Welcome Center,&nbsp;</strong>1001 Ocean Drive</p>



<p>[Disclosure: I work here] What would Miami Beach be like without Art Deco? Spend a morning at the Art Deco Welcome Center — start with a walking tour from a Miami Design Preservation League guide, then explore the exhibits in the Art Deco Museum and take something home from the Art Deco Gift Shop.</p>



<p><strong>Tip:</strong>&nbsp;Admission to the museum is free for Miami-Dade County residents, tour tickets are $30. Visit&nbsp;<a href="https://mdpl.org/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">mdpl.org</a>&nbsp;for information.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Mid Beach</h3>



<p><strong>Muss Park,&nbsp;</strong>4300 Chase Ave.</p>



<p>Miami Beach is full of neighborhood parks, and Muss Park recently underwent a lengthy renovation. It ranks among my young niece and nephew’s favorite local parks. Situated along the Biscayne Waterway, enjoy the kids’ playground while you watch kayakers row by.</p>



<p><strong>Tip:</strong>&nbsp;If you stay long enough, you’re likely to see dolphins and manatees.</p>



<p><strong>Miami Beach Beachwalk,&nbsp;</strong>from South Pointe Park to 87th Street and Collins Avenue</p>



<p>One of the country’s most impressive urban projects is right in our backyard. Over the last several decades, the City of Miami Beach has created a beachwalk that within the past year, provides a continuous, car-free path from South Pointe Park to 87th street and Collins (the northern city limits).</p>



<p>Walk, bike, or roller skate along the beachwalk. You’ll see the evolution of Miami Beach’s neighborhoods and the ocean side of many of our historic districts, with peeks out to the beautiful Atlantic Ocean at different moments throughout the undulating path.</p>



<p><strong>Tip:</strong>&nbsp;Visit in the late afternoon to benefit from the sun being on the west side of the buildings, which will provide additional shade for your journey.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">North Beach</h3>



<p><strong>North Beach Oceanside Park,&nbsp;</strong>Collins Avenue between 78th and 87th streets</p>



<p>Originally a single-family neighborhood, the land at the northern end of the city was converted in the 1970s to expand public park space. It may not be as well known as its South Beach counterparts, but this park is full of amenities like a playground, picnic tables, a dog park, mature shade trees, and meandering paths. Not to mention the beach runs the length of the park on the east side — and is generally less crowded than South Beach.</p>



<p><strong>Tip:</strong>&nbsp;Head over on a sunny day to walk under the mature trees — it’s about 10 degrees cooler under the shade</p>



<p><strong>North Beach Bandshell,&nbsp;</strong>7275 Collins Ave.</p>



<p>Recently designated as a local historic landmark, the North Beach Bandshell is not only an important mid-century modern landmark, but has helped spearhead the revitalization of the area. The <a href="https://www.rhythmfoundation.com/#/events" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Rhythm Foundation</a> does a great job producing diverse programs that have made it a go-to hub for residents and visitors. A newly designed canopy helps provide shade and rain protection.<strong>Tip:</strong> Bookmark the bandshell’s event listings, which are updated throughout the year on its website: <a href="https://www.northbeachbandshell.com/events#/events">https://www.northbeachbandshell.com/events#/events</a></p>



<p><em>Daniel Ciraldo is the executive director of the Miami Design Preservation League, the Miami Beach nonprofit that works to preserve the city’s historic architecture.</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://un.online.mills.edu/explore-miami-beach-from-the-bottom-to-the-top-here-are-some-of-its-hidden-gems/">Explore Miami Beach from the bottom to the top. Here are some of its hidden gems</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://un.online.mills.edu">UN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://un.online.mills.edu/explore-miami-beach-from-the-bottom-to-the-top-here-are-some-of-its-hidden-gems/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
